Newland/Zeuner Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Vocal Music (Box 24-46, Box 56)
  - Sacred vocal music: Latin (Box 24-35)
    - Motets, anthems, antiphones, etc. - Manuscripts (Box 31-35)
      - Bone Pastor (Box 32)
        - Rossini, Gioacchino
          - Bone Pastor, organ/vocal score, basso part (Box 32)
      - Crudeles Herodes (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Crudeles Herodes see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald, Box 32
      - Date sonitum pastores (Box 32)
        - Costa, M.
          - Date sonitum pastores, Offertorium for Bass & Coro; organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Deo gloria (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Deo gloria, vocal parts, organ score with text; also includes: Chant Easter (vocal part) (Box 32)
      - Deus tu orum (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Deus tu orum see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
      - Dona nobis pacem (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Dona nobis pacem, fragments; organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Domine dominus noster (Box 32)
        - Weiss, L.
          - Domine dominus noster, soprano and bass parts, organ/vocal score; [inside printed cover page] Duett for Soprano & Bass (Box 32)
      - Ecce Deus Salvator Meus (Box 32)
        - Clifton, J. C.
          - Ecce Deus Salvator Meus, basso part; also includes: O Salutaris by Bordese, basso part. (Box 32)
      - Ecce panis angelorum (Box 32)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Ecce panis angelorum, organ/vocal score; fragment (Box 32)
      - Emitte spiritum (Box 32)
        - Webbe, Samuel
          - Emitte spiritum, vocal parts; Hymn for Whitsuntide (Box 32)
      - E viva Maria (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - E viva Maria see: Jesu Mater, arr. by André
      - Exultet orbis (Box 32)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - Exultet orbis, organ/vocal score; also includes: Iste Confessor, by Ohnewald. Arranged by W. A. Newland (Box 32)
      - Gratias agimus tibi (Box 32)
        - Guglielmi, Pietro
          - Gratias agimus tibi, soprano part (solo); fragment (Box 32)
      - Iam sol recedit (Box 32)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - Iam sol recedit see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
      - In Festo... (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - In Festo..., organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Inviolata integra (Box 32)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Inviolata integra, [2 settings] Duo [vocal score] and Solo; organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Iste confessor (Box 32)
        - Handel, George Frideric
          - Iste confessor, Aria from Rinaldo (Box 32)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - Iste confessor see: Exultet Orbis, by Ohnewald Box 32
      - Jesu Dei vivi (Box 26)
        - Verdi, Giuseppe
          - Jesu Dei vivi see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
      - Jesu dulcis memoria (Box 32)
        - Müller, D.
          - Jesu dulcis memoria, Op. 77, organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Jesu Filii Dei (Box 26)
        - Winter
          - Jesu Filii Dei see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
      - Jesu, Jesu (Box 31)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Jesu, Jesu see: Mascagni, Ave Maria, Box 31
      - Jesu Mater (Box 32)
        - André (arranger)
          - Jesu Mater, organ/vocal score; from Mozart's Die Zauberflöte; Includes: E viva Maria. Chorus as sung in Italy by the congregations, after each verse of the various hymns which are used. Decora lux eternitas, by Ohnewald, arr. by Newland (Box 32)
      - Jesu Mellifluus (Box 26)
        - Schneider, F.
          - Jesu Mellifluus see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
      - Jesu Redemptor omnium (Box 32)
        - Mercadente, Saverio
          - Jesu Redemptor omnium, organ/vocal score (Box 32)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - Jesu Redemptor omnium, organ/vocal score (Box 32)
      - Laudate Dominum (Box 32)
        - Vogler, Georg Joseph
          - Laudate Dominum, tenor and organ parts; from Lyra Catholica, p. 260 (Box 32)
      - Laudate pueri Dominum (Box 32)
        - Zingarelli, Nicolo
          - Laudate pueri Dominum, vocal parts (Box 32)
      - Libera me Domine (Box 32)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Libera me Domine, vocal score (Box 32)
      - Liber scriptus (Box 32)
        - Ohnewald, J.
          - Liber scriptus, scored for tenor solo, 2 violins and organ; Arranged by W. A. Newland; Includes: Deus tu orum, setting of Iam sol recedit by Ohnewald; Veni Creator, arr. by Newland Crudeles Herodes, setting of (Box 32)
      - Lucis Creator (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Lucis Creator (Box 32)
      - Magnificat (Box 32)
        - Bühler, F.
          - Magnificat, vocal score; [printed cover page] III Magnificats (Nos. 1-3) (Box 32)
        - Wittig, Carl
          - Magnificat see: Regina coeli, by Giorza, Box 33
      - Mater admirabilis (Box 32)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Mater admirabilis, solo vocal and organ parts (Box 32)
      - Memorare (Box 32)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Memorare, vocal parts (Box 32)
      - Miserere (Box 33)
        - Baij, Tomasso
          - Miserere, vocal score and parts (Box 33)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Miserere, vocal parts (Box 33)
        - Winter
          - Miserere, Trio for alto, tenor and bass; vocal parts (Box 33)
      - O cor amoris (Box 33)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - O cor amoris, vocal parts and organ/vocal score (Box 33)
      - O Gloriosa Domina (Box 33)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - O Gloriosa Domina, tenor part and organ score with text (Box 33)
      - O Jesu Deus (Box 33)
        - Haydn, Franz Joseph
          - O Jesu Deus see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
        - Mercadente, Saverio
          - O Jesu Deus, vocal score; Arranged by W. A. Newland; Duetto from Il Giuramento (Box 33)
        - Webbe, Samuel
          - O Jesu Deus, organ/vocal score; also includes: Glory to God by Dielman (trumpet solo) (Box 33)
        - Winter
          - O Jesu Deus, organ/vocal score and organ score with text; Arranged by W. A. Newland (Box 33)
      - O Jesu Jesu (Box 26)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - O Jesu Jesu see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
      - O Jesu pastor bonus (Box 33)
        - Winter
          - O Jesu pastor bonus, vocal score and part (Box 33)
      - O salutaris hostia (Box 33)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - O salutaris hostia see: Clifton, Ecce Deus Salvator Meus, Box 32
        - Cherubini, Luigi
          - O salutaris hostia see: Haydn, Mass in B-flat, Box 26
        - Pecher, W. F.
          - O salutaris hostia see: Ave Maria (Mascagni)
        - [Unidentified]
          - O salutaris hostia, 3 folders (Box 33)
      - O vos omnes (Box 33)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - O vos omnes (Box 33)
      - Quid retribuam (Box 33)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Quid retribuam, soprano solo and choral parts (Box 33)
      - Regina coeli (Box 33)
        - Giorza, Paolo
          - Regina coeli, organ score with text; also includes: Magnificat by Carl Wittig (Box 33)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Regina coeli, vocal parts (Box 33)
        - Rosewig, Albert H.
          - Regina coeli, instrumental parts (Box 33)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Regina coeli (Box 33)
      - Regina terrae (Box 33)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Regina terrae, vocal parts (Box 33)
      - Resurrexit (Box 33)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Resurrexit, vocal parts (Box 33)
      - Sancta Maria (Box 33)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Sancta Maria, vocal score and parts, instrumental parts (Box 33)
      - Salve Maria (Box 33)
        - Mercadente, Saverio
          - Salve Maria, organ/vocal score, vocal parts (Box 33)
      - Salve Regina (Box 33)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Salve Regina (Box 33)
      - Stabat Mater (Box 34)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Stabat Mater, vocal and instrumental parts (Box 34)
        - Rossini, Gioacchino
          - Stabat Mater, organ with text; Includes: instrumental parts for Pro peccatis (No. 4) tenor and instrumental parts for Inflammatus (No. 8) organ/vocal score for Cujus animam string parts for Eia! Mater (Box 34)
      - Stella coeli (Box 34)
        - Dreyer, J. M.
          - Stella coeli, organ/vocal score (Box 34)
      - Sub tuum (Box 34)
        - Diehlman
          - Sub tuum, organ/vocal score (Box 34)
      - Tantum Ergo (Box 34)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Tantum Ergo, organ/vocal score, vocal parts (Box 34)
        - Rossi
          - Tantum Ergo, vocal parts (Box 34)
        - Thunder, H. G.
          - Tantum Ergo, vocal parts (Box 34)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Tantum Ergo (Box 34)
      - Te Deum (Box 34)
        - Carr, Benjamin
          - Te Deum, organ score with text (Box 34)
        - Handel, George Frideric
          - Te Deum, organ/vocal score, string parts (Box 34)
        - Haydn, Franz Joseph
          - Te Deum see: Haydn, Mass in D, No. 3, Box 26
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Te Deum, vocal parts (Box 34)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Te Deum see: Haydn, Mass in D, No. 3, Box 26
        - Newland, William Augustine (harmonizer)
          - Te Deum, vocal score (Box 34)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Te Deum, setting for organ with text (Box 34)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Te Deum, string parts (Box 34)
      - Tota Pulchra (Box 35)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Tota Pulchra, vocal score (Box 35)
      - Veni Creator (Box 35)
        - Newland, William Augustine (arranger)
          - Veni Creator see: Liber scriptus, by Ohnewald Box 32
        - [Unidentified]
          - Veni Creator (Box 35)
      - Venite Adoremus (Box 35)
        - Gelsin, M. A.
          - Venite Adoremus, vocal parts (Box 35)
      - Venite filii (Box 35)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Venite filii, organ/vocal score (Box 35)
      - Vexilla regis (Box 35)
        - Donizetti, Gaetano
          - Vexilla regis, organ/vocal score; Arranged by W. A. Newland (Box 35)
      - Vir Fideles (Box 35)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Vir Fideles, vocal parts (Box 35)
      - Vivat pastor (Box 35)
        - [Unidentified]
          - Vivat pastor - Song of Welcome for a Bishop or Pastor, vocal score (Box 35)
      - Litanies and Service music (Box 35)
        - [Litanies] (Box 35)
        - [Service music - compilation] (Box 35)
        - [Service music - miscellaneous] (Box 35)
    - Instrumental parts to sacred vocal music with Latin text (Box 35)
      - Ave Maria (Box 35)
        - Lambillotte, Louis
          - Ave Maria, violin 2 (Box 35)
      - Ave Regina (Box 35)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - Ave Regina, organ part (Box 35)
      - Exulta Zion (Box 35)
        - Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
          - Exulta Zion, full orchestra (Box 35)
      - Gage d'amitie (Box 35)
        - Viereck
          - Gage d'amitie, Op. XVI [variations], viola part (Box 35)
      - Gloria (Box 35)
        - Cornopean
          - Gloria, horn part (Box 35)
      - Gratias agimus tibi (Box 35)
        - Gulielmus
          - Gratias agimus tibi, violin obligato, clarinet (Box 35)
      - O Salutaris (Box 35)
        - Cherubini, Luigi
          - O Salutaris, viola part (Box 35)
      - Stabat mater (Box 35)
        - Raffelin, A.
          - Stabat mater, clarinet part; Includes: Miserere Introduction to the Three Hours [Agony] (Box 35)
      - Compilations (Box 35)
        - [Compilation of organ accompaniments] (Box 35)
        - [Compilations of string accompaniments (v. 2, vc. and bs.)] (Box 35)
  - Sacred vocal music: Non-Latin (Box 36-41, Box 56)
    - Works for voice and orchestra - Printed music (Box 36)
      - Haydn, Franz Joseph
        - Die Worte des Erlösers am Kreuze, in Musik gesezt von Joseph Haydn. In Partitur. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel, n.d. (Box 36)
        - The Creation, an Oratorio composed by Joseph Haydn. Arranged for the Organ or Piano Forte by Muzio Clementi. Improved from the first American Edition with Verbal Emendations from the latest London Edition. Boston: Handel and Haydn Society, 1827., Signed by W. A. Newland (Box 36)
    - Works for voice and orchestra - Manuscripts (Box 36-37, Box 56)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van
        - Mount of Olives; Alleluja Chorus see: Haydn, Mass in C, No. 2, Box 26
      - Calcott, J. W.
        - These as they change, Almighty Father, orchestral score; copied by Charles Zeuner (Box 36)
      - Crotch, William
        - Palestine; Recitative and aria, orchestral score with text; copied by Charles Zeuner (Box 36)
      - Handel, George Frideric
        - Angels ever bright and fair - Larghetto [V. 1 & 2 parts] (Box 36)
      - Haydn, Franz Joseph
        - Creation, tenor part (Box 36)
        - The Seasons, instrumental parts (Box 37)
        - Seven Last Words, piano accompaniment (Box 37)
        - Seven Last Words; Introduzione, instrumental parts (Box 37)
      - Mason, Lowell
        - The Lord our God is clothed with might, orchestral score; copied by Charles Zeuner (Box 37)
      - Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
        - David; Chorus - Behold the Giant (Box 56)
      - Newland, William Augustine
        - [12] Te Deum[s], vocal and instrumental parts (Box 37)
      - Raffelin, A.
        - Villansicos para la Noche de Navidad a 4 voces con acompañamiento de Orquesta (Op. 78), instrumental parts (Box 37)
    - Works for voice and keyboard or a cappella voices - Printed music (Box 38-39)
      - By Composer (Box 38)
        - Adam, Adolphe
          - Noël [with] Orgue Mélodium par A. Adam., Pl. no. 11539. (Box 38)
        - Clasing, I. H.
          - Canon aus dem Oratorium: Belsazar. In Musik gesetzt von I. H. Clasing. (Beilage zur allgem. musickalischen Zeitung 1825. No. 52; No. VI). (Box 38)
        - Emerick, Albert G.
          - Sacred Sentences from the Bible, Designed as introductory pieces for public worship, Selected and Composed, with an accompaniment for the organ by Albert G. Emerick. Book II. Philadelphia: G. B. Zieber & Co., 1846., Title page only (Box 38)
        - Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
          - Canon aus der Ostermorgen von S. Neukomm. (Beilage zur allgemeinen musikalischen eitung. 1824. No. III, 20.) (Box 38)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Te Deum Laudamus for four voices with an accompaniment for the Organ or Piano Forte by William Augustine Newland. Baltimore: W. C. Peters, 1848., Peters Collection of Popular Sacred Music. No. 703) Pl. no. 164.-17.; 2 copies (Box 38)
        - Werner, Arno (harmonizer)
          - Forth comes the standard (Vexilla Regis), Jesus Crucified, [and] At the Cross Her Station Keeping. Harmonized by A. Werner. Boston: O. Ditson & Co., n.d., Ditson & Co.s Sacred Selections. 18th series. No. 1840 (Box 38)
        - Zingarelli, Nicolo
          - Fuga a 4 di Nicolo Zingarelli. (Beilage zur allgem. musikalischen Zeitung. 1821. No. 52; No. V). (Box 38)
        - [Unidentified]
          - An Gott. [Der du mit Weisheit... ] (Box 38)
      - Collections (Box 38-39)
        - The Boston Handel and Haydn Society Collection of Sacred Music. Vol. II Boston: Handel and Haydn Society, 1823. (Box 38)
        - The Boston Handel and Haydn Society Collection of Sacred Music. Vol. IV Boston: Handel and Haydn Society, 1832. (Box 38)
        - The Choral Harmonist. Vol. 3, No. 25-32. London: J. Hart, n.d. (Box 39)
        - Handel & Haydn Collection., From the 4th volume.; 5 copies; Includes: Palestrina - We have heard with our ears. [Kent] - Te Deum. Haydn - Te Deum. Beethoven - March and Chorus of Roman Soldiers from the Mount of Olives. (Box 39)
    - Works for voice and keyboard or a cappella voices - Manuscripts (Box 39-41, Box 56)
      - By Composer (Box 39-40, Box 56)
        - Bordese, Luigi
          - Flowers of Sacred Harmony (Box 39)
        - Carr, Benjamin
          - Anthem for Christmas, soprano and basso parts (Box 39)
          - Jubilate Deo (O be joyful), vocal parts (Box 39)
          - Jubilate Deo (with a Gloria by Charles Zeuner) (Box 56)
        - Cunnington, W. P.
          - 3 Dirges - Sung at the Solemn Requiem at St. Joseph's Church on March 18, 1863, organ score with text (Box 39)
        - Greene, Maurice
          - Duet - The Lord is my shepherd, organ/vocal score (Box 39)
        - Handel, George Frideric
          - Athalia, organ/vocal score (Box 39)
        - Hansen, E. R.
          - When shall we meet again - A sacred hymn, organ/vocal score (Box 39)
        - Harwood
          - Funeral Anthem, organ/vocal score; copied by Charles Zeuner (Box 39)
        - Jackson, William
          - Anthem - Turn ye to me, vocal score (Box 39)
        - Jones, Geo. F.
          - Krug, contralto part and organ score with text (Box 39)
        - Meignen, Leopold
          - [Compilation of sacred and secular vocal works], piano and piano/vocal scores (Box 39)
        - Milelotti, G.
          - La Pentecosta, organ/vocal score (Box 39)
        - Moran, P. K.
          - The Hebrew Mourner, organ/vocal score; Words by J. W. Eastburn (Box 39)
        - Neukomm, Sigismund Ritter von
          - O Jesus my Redeemer, organ/vocal score; Words from the German of Klopstock (Box 39)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Fairest Virgin, vocal parts (Box 40)
          - [Te Deum], organ/vocal score (Box 40)
          - Te Deum Laudamus, orchestral and organ/vocal scores (Box 40)
        - Newland, William Augustine
          - Grand Te Deum, organ/vocal score (Box 40)
        - Rosenthal, W.
          - Spirit Creator, organ score with text (Box 40)
        - Spohr, Louis
          - Blessed are the dead, vocal score; This dirge was performed at the memorial services of Gen. U. S. Grant, Aug. 5, 1885 (Box 40)
        - Stradella, Alessandro
          - Air D'Eglise (Pieta Signore), vocal parts (Box 40)
        - Tuckerman, S. Parkman
          - Anthem - Sing praises to God (Box 40)
      - Title only (Box 40-41, Box 56)
        - As the Hart Panteth, organ/vocal score (Box 40)
        - Mary Our Lovely Queen of May, organ score with text (Box 40)
        - O my Redeemer, organ/vocal score (Box 40)
        - We praise thee O God / Te Deum, organ/vocal score (Box 40)
        - [Anglican chants copied by Charles Zeuner], Includes: Benedic anima mea Benedictus Bonum est confiteri Deus Miseratur Gloria Patri Glorious Mother Jubilate Deo Venite Exultemus Domino (Box 40)
        - [Compilation of litanies, etc.] (Box 40)
        - [Hymn parts] (Box 56)
        - [Miscellaneous chants] (Box 40)
        - [Miscellaneous hymn parts] (Box 40)
        - [Miscellaneous works] (Box 40)
        - [Miscellaneous fragments] (Box 40)
        - Instrumental parts, sacred vocal, non-Latin (Box 41)
  - Secular vocal music (Box 41-46, Box 56)
    - Music for 1 voice - Printed music (Box 41-42, Box 56)
      - By Composer (Box 41-42)
        - Arne, Thomas Augustine
          - (The wanton God who pierces hearts... ) Sung by Mrs. Clive. [London?]: [s.n.], n.d. (Box 41)
        - Beethoven, Ludwig van
          - Gesänge mit Begleitung des Klaviers in Musik gesetzt von L. van Beethoven. No. 16. [Op. 52, no. 5] Mayence: Charles Zulehner, n.d., Pl. no. 113. (Box 41)
          - May Gesang. Wieherrlich Leuchtet mir die Natur von Göthe [and] Ohne Liebe Lebe, wer da Kann Gedicht von Lessing, in Musik gesezt mit Clavier Begleitung von L. van Beethoven. No. 11 u. 12. Mainz: B. Schott Söhne, [1788?]., Pl. no. 109. (Box 41)
          - Scena ed Aria, Ha! Treuloser Meineidger verräthrischer Barbar? = (Ah! perfido, spergiuro barbaro traditor) in Musik gesezt mit Clavier Begleitung von L. van Beethoven. No. 13. Mainz: B. Schott Söhne, [1805?]., Pl. no. 150. (Box 41)
        - Bellini, Vincenzo
          - Beatrice di Tenda. Come t'adoro e quanto, cavatina nella Beatrice di Tenda del maestro Bellini. Paris: Pacini, n.d., Pl. no. 3360. (Box 41)
          - La Sonnambula. Ah non credea mirarti. Air Finale per voce di soprano. Paris: V. Launer, n.d., Pl. no. V.L. 3199. (Box 41)
        - Bertoni, Ferdinando Gioseffo
          - La Virginella. Adapted as a favorite Lesson for the Harpsichord [S.l.]: [s.n.], [1780?]. (Box 41)
        - Bordogni, Giulio Marco
          - 24 nouvelles Vocalises faciles et progressives à la portée de toutes les voix avec piano par Marco Bordogni. Introduction aux 36 Vocalises. Livr. I. Berlin: A. M. Schlesinger, n.d., Pl. no. S. 3566(1). (Box 41)
        - Bornhardt, J. H. C.
          - Das Musikalische Tempo. Ein Gesang mit Begleitung der Guitarre. Zur Erbauung für jedes Alter. Gedichtet von Haug. Componirt von J. H. C. Bornhardt. Braunschweig: I. P. Spehr, n.d., Pl. no. 1129. (Box 41)
          - Der Taucher, Ballade von Schiller zur Guitarre componirt von J.H.C. Bornhardt. 65tes Werck. Braunschweig: J. P. Spehr, n.d., Pl. no. 973. (Box 41)
        - Della Maria, Pierre-Antoine-Dominique
          - Le Prisonnier Aria aus der Oper le Prisonier. Wenn ich in jenen finstern Mauern. Mainz: B. Schott, [1819?]., Pl. no. 7. (Box 41)
          - Romance. No. 18. Le Prisonnier ou la Ressemblance. Paroles du Duval, Musique du Delamaria. [Paris]: J. Mees, n.d., from Journal hebdomadaire (Box 41)
        - Dibdin, Charles
          - Brother Jack, written & composed by Mr. Dibdin, and sung by him in his new entertainment called the Cake House. London: Charles Dibdin, n.d. (Box 41)
          - The Miller's Wedding Day. Composed by Mr. C. Dibdin. [London]: C. S. T., n.d. (Box 41)
        - Fisher, John Abraham
          - The Morning Invitation, a Cantata by A. Fisher. [London]: M. W., [1775?]. (Box 41)
        - Ford, J.
          - The Resolution. Set by Mr. J. Ford. [London]: C. S. T., n.d. (Box 41)
        - Handel, George Frideric
          - Aria (Lascia ch'io pianga) from Rinaldo by Handel. [S.l.]: G. André & Co., 1863., Pl. no. G. A. & Co. 812.; English words by S. B. W. (Box 41)
        - Hook, James
          - For none but thee I'll marry. Sung by Mrs. Kennedy at Vauxhall. Set by Mr. Hook. [London]: Skillern, [17-]. (Box 41)
        - Kuhlau, Friedrich
          - Deutsche Gesänge mit Begleitung des Piano-Forte von Friedrich Kuhlau. 19tes Werk, 2te Samml. Lieder. Hamburg: Aug. Cranz, n.d., Title page only (Box 41)
        - Lamparelli, Antoine
          - Romances avec accompagnement de Piano ou Harpe tirées du Roman de Sabina, musique de Lamparelli. Paris: H. Naderman, n.d., Pl. no. 450. (Box 41)
        - Linley, Thomas
          - Carnival of Venice (Box 41)
          - In My Pleasant Native Plains. Composed by Mr. Linley. London: S. A. & P. Thompson, [1781]. (Box 41)
        - Martin y Soler, Vicente
          - Baum der Diana. Aria. Doristo. Nro. 4. Bonn: N. Simrock, n.d., Pl. no. 27. (Box 41)
          - Lilla. Aria. Warum ward mir nicht vergennet von V. Martin. Nro. 20. München: Gotzischen Verlag, n.d., Pl. no. 223. (Box 41)
        - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
          - Abend-empfindung (Abend ist's, die Sonn e ist verschwunden) mit Pianoforte Begleitung von Mozart. Mainz: B. Schott Söhnen, n.d., Pl. no. 1377. (Box 41)
          - Die Entführung aus dem Serail Arie. Ach! ich Liebte, war so glücklich, Kannte, etc. (Loin de l'object de ma tendresse) von W. A. Mozart. Clavierauszug. Hamburg: Johann August Böhme, n.d. (Box 41)
          - Romanze. In Mohrenland gefangen war (Dans un chateau de l'Arragon) von W. A. Mozart. Clavierauszug. Hamburg: Johann August Böhme, n.d. (Box 41)